A little further down.
ちょっと下まで
Can I try my best to open it?
頑張って開いていい?
Should I open it?
開いちゃおうかな
Where inside?
どこの中?
In this.
この中
I'm sorry.
申し訳ございません
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It will be well known.
よくばれるでしょ
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
Without survival.
健存なしで
How many centimeters are you tall?
身長は何センチぐらいですか?
It's about 160.
160くらいです
I just mentioned something quite expensive.
さっき結構高いこと入ってたんでね
Think of it as Saint Khyber.
そう いうのをセントカイバーと思ってね
So I did a lot of that.
だから 結構あれやったんで
is that so.
そう ですか
That's nice.
いいですね
There was a little sparkle in her eyes as she walked towards me.
歩いてくる姿にちょっとキラキラしてました
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Well, I'd like you to tell me some things.
じゃあいろいろ教えてほしいんですけど
Are there any travelers now?
今、旅手はいてますか?
I'm not there right now.
今はいないです
Huh, how much is it?
え、どんくらいだっけな?
About 3 or 4 months.
3、4ヶ月ぐらいです
About 3 or 4 months?
3、4ヶ月ぐらい?
now
今
Because I feel lonely.
は 寂しいからね
I agree.
そうですね
is that so.
そうですか
Well, there's something lonely about not being there for about 3 or 4 months.
まあ、3、4ヶ月ぐらいはいてないってことは 寂しいものがある
Isn't it?
じゃない ですか
surely.
確かに
What do you do on those days?
そういう日はどうするんですか?
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Does that mean I'm doing something embarrassing?
恥ずかしいことしてるってことですか?
I'm a bit embarrassed so I'll keep it a secret.
恥ずかしいんでちょっと内緒です
Well, that's just what we imagine.
そんな、まあまあじゃあ 僕らが想像してるようなことってこと
That's right.
ですね
Or do you feel embarrassed about something different?
それ ともなんか違うことでも恥ずかしいことがあるんですか?
I really listen to it.
めっちゃ聞きますね
That's already an important point.
それはもうそこは重要なところなんで
What do you think?
どうですか?
Eh, ok.
えー、まあまあ
Self.
セルフで
How many times did you have your first experience?
初 体験はいくつぐらいですか?
First experience...
初体験...
5, 3, etc.
5、3とか
17、18
Was your first partner a boyfriend?
ちゃんと初めての相手は彼氏あったんですか?
no.
いや
Surprisingly, there are people like that.
意外とね、そういう方いてますよね
Is that wrong?
それは違うんですか?
That's not true.
違いますね
Who is that person?
その人は何者なんですか?
I am a senior at my part-time job.
バイトの先輩です
Even after that, we never started dating?
付き合ったりすることもなくその後も?
Yeah.
うん
Oh my.
あらまあ
We worked part-time together and became good friends,
それは、バイトも一緒にやって仲良くなって、
Like, let's go out somewhere, or after I finish my part-time job.
どこか遊びに行こうよとか、それからバイト終わった後にとか、
What was it like?
どんな感じだったんですか?
After we were done talking, I went to the house,
終わって、喋ってたら家に行って、
Like.
みたいな
Would you like to come to my house?
家に来ないかい?
Like.
みたいな
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Isn't it hidden?
隠しなんじゃないですか?
I guess I'm a bit of a senior at that part-time job.
ちょっとそのバイトの先輩というか、
Did you think it was a little better?
少しは良いなと思ってたんですか?
The face.
顔が
After all, handsome men are special.
や っぱり、イケメンは特殊だということですね
So I went to that house.
それでその家に行きました
What happened from there?
そこからどうなったんですか?
From there?
そこから?
yes.
はい
enter.
入ります
I come in and talk.
入って喋ってます
Should I watch TV or listen to music?
テレビでも見ようか、もしくは音楽聞こうかとかあるじゃない
Is it?
ですか
What was it like?
ど んな感じだったんですか?
I was watching online.
ネットフリ見てて
Look at me.
見てて
I'm sitting next to you.
横に座ってます
in?
で?
If you notice.
気づいたら
Before you know it, it's a spa?
気づいたらスパだか?
That's not it.
それはない
No, there is.
いやいや、ありますよ
There is.
あるんだ
I was reading My Girl at home and watching Netflix.
僕の女の子を家読んでネットフリックス見てたら、
Does that mean you've become flashy all of a sudden?
いつの間にか派手派手になってるってことですか?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
How was it?
どうでした?
My impressions after finishing it for the first time,
初めてのその終わった後の感想っていうか、
It's called a change of state of mind.
心境の変化という
Hey.
へぇー
It didn't really hurt or anything?
痛かったとかも特に無く?
especially.
特に
Even though it was painful, it stays in your memory quite a lot, right?
痛かったところで結構記憶に残るじゃないですか
The fact that there wasn't one didn't mean I was that particular about it.
無かったってことは、別にそんなにスンナリいったというか
Is that so?
そうですかね
Don't be my boyfriend and get away with it.
彼氏にならず、平たくでやり逃げと
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうですね
I feel like I should make it into a better memory.
もうちょっといい思い出にしろって感じなんですけど
is that so.
そうですか
I think a lot has happened since then.
そこからいろいろあったと思うんですけど、
I wonder if this was an abnormal thing compared to humans.
ちょっとこれは人と比べて、アブノーマルやったんじゃないかな、
A play like that.
みたいなプレイとか
Cars, etc.
車とか、
I don't think so.
ない 気がする
On the other hand, I've never done it before, but I'm a little scared.
逆に、やっとしたことないけど、ちょっと恐怖があるぞってこと
No?
ない ですか?
Hey.
ねえ
Because I don't know much about it.
詳しくないから
I agree.
そうですね
In terms of topics, there are multiple,
ネタの辺でいうと、複数であったり、
It's kind of long though.
長いであったりっていうところなんですけど
What do you think?
どうですか?
Maybe more than one?
複数とかかな?
Tamiyal.
タミヤルな
Which pattern is better for men or women?
それは、男に女にどっちのパターンがいいんですか?
Or for a couple?
それともカップルに?
Or something.
とか
Maybe I wouldn't be so nervous if it was a man.
男にの方が緊張しないかもしれない
wonderful.
素晴らしい
That's the best answer.
最高のお答えです
Why, two people?
なんでさ、2人に
Oh, no.
あ、じゃない
Does that mean it's okay to have two good-looking guys?
イケメン2人やったらいいってことですか?
I'm sure.
確か
That's nice.
いいですね
Are you a normal scout?
普通のスカウトなんですか?
yes.
はい
Isn't it the one with innerwear that people often fool?
よく騙されるインナーが入ってるやつではないですか?
No.
違います
wonderful.
素晴らしい
Can I ask you to raise it a little higher yourself?
自分で少し上にあげてもらっていいですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It would be nice if you could give it to me while saying that.
って言いながらあげてくれるのがいいですね
A little more, a little more.
もう少し、もう少し
One more person.
もう、もうひと
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's like you can see it, but you can't, and it's like you can see it.
見えそうで見えないような、見えてるような
The top and bottom are not connected, right?
それ、上と下はつながってないですよね、
Normally.
普通にね
It's divided.
分かれてます
Does this have a zipper?
これ、ジッパーになってるんですか?
yes.
そう
Now, I'd like you to loosen the zipper a little bit.
じゃあ、ジッパーを少しちょっと緩めてもらって
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
You'll pull it out while saying that, right?
って言いながら抜いてくれるんでしょ?
Take your time and put it down.
じっくり時間をかけて下ろすのね
wonderful.
素晴らしい
Just a little more.
もうちょい
No, that's all.
いや、もう全部ですね
all?
全部?
When you get to the bottom, it separates.
下まで行ったら分かれるんですよね
Just a little further down.
ちょっと、下まで
Wait, what should I say beyond that?
ちょっと、その上の、何と言ったらいいんでしょう
this?
これ?
yes.
はい
Can I take it out for a moment?
ちょっと、抜いてもらってもいいですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Uncle, can you stare at me?
おじさん、じろじろ見られるの?
It might be embarrassing.
恥ずかしいかもしれない
That's a good thing.
いいことですよ
Just leave it there, have me hold it behind you,
そのままね、そこを後ろに持たれてもらって、
Can I have you spread your legs in an M shape?
足をM字に開いてもらっていいですか?
M word?
M字?
Good.
よいしょ
I've heard this many times, but what do you think?
何回も聞きますけど、どうですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですね
From now on, I'm going to ask you to do something even more embarrassing.
これからね、もっと恥ずかしいことしてもらうんですけど
What do you think of this embarrassing pose?
どうですか、この恥ずかしいポーズは?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですね
Didn't you just say that after we broke up?
さっき言ってたじゃないですか、 別れた後、
You're doing something embarrassing.
恥ずかしいことしてるんですよね
Is this it?
それは、これですか?
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあまあ
まあまあまあ
I wonder if I'll find out if I try it?
試したら分かるかな
Does that mean I'm still doing this all by myself?
このまま一人で、こういうことをしてるってことですか?
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Sorry, the fabric for this pose is stiff,
ちょっとね、このポーズ生地が硬いんで、
Can I get Kuri-chan's person?
くりちゃんの人もらってもいいですか?
This is the one that changes the temperature of Kuri-chan.
くりちゃんを気温にするやつです
With different feelings, being sucked by Kuri-chan,
ちがう気持ちで、くりちゃんを吸われてるのと、
I'm putting this hot water in.
この湯を入れてるの
I don't know.
分かんない
both.
両方
How do you feel good?
どうやると気持ちいいんですか?
Like when I do it at home.
家でやってる時みたいに
What to do with your hair?
髪の毛をどうする?
Really?
めっちゃ?
What are you going to do after this?
この後どうするんですか?
What should I do?
どうする?
This big one.
この大きくなったやつを
What should I do?
どうする?
Look.
ほら
You can have Ori-san pull down your pants while you put it in.
その入れたまんま、 おりさんのパンツをずらしてもらってもいい
Is it?
ですか?
Please come over here with me.
一 緒に、こっちに来てもらって
Should I lick it?
舐めればいい?
too
も
Chiron.
ち ろん
Does it feel good?
気持ちよく?
Can I count it?
数えてもいい?
So, what about the one from earlier?
じゃあ、さっきのやつは?
No, right?
ないでしょ
There are usually more.
普段はもっと多いってことだね
Is it okay if I come here?
こっちに来てもらっても大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
I had my uncle's horns pulled in.
おじさんのツブを引っ込みてもらってました
I'm trying to get it to come out.
出させようとしてるんですけど
delicious?
おいしい?
Does that mean it's not delicious?
おいしくないってこと?
Which one?
どっち?
It's delicious.
おいしいです
100 points?
100点の?
It's the best.
最高です
Were there a lot?
いっぱい出てた?
There were a lot of them.
いっぱい出てました
I was drinking.
飲んじゃいました
What does it taste like?
どんな味なんですか?
どんな味?
Isn't it delicious?
やっぱおいしくない?
Delicious.
おいしくは
Too much?
出すぎ?
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
I'm bringing it nearby.
近くに持ってきてますけど
Are you feeling better?
元気になってますか?
Yuan
元
air.
気
Can you give me your uncle's one?
お じさんのやつにかけてくれる?
wonderful.
素晴らしい
What do you do with the one you like?
気に入るやつはどうするんですか?
What should we do?
どうしましょう?
What do you want?
どうしてほしいんですか?
Towards the camera.
カメラに向かって
I want you to enter it.
入 れてほしい
Inside.
中に
Where inside?
どこの中?
Yeah.
うん
If you can get on that.
それに乗ってくれたら
Are you in here?
おまえこの中?
Please get your knees up.
膝をね、立ててもらって
Now you can move up and down like this.
これでこう上下に動ける
Please take care.
おそそそ
Come forward.
前に来て
Can you move like this yourself?
自分でこう動ける?
knees.
膝
Be in a position that allows you to move easily.
動きやすい姿勢で
Even higher.
もっと上まで
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Put your hands behind your back.
後ろに手をついて
Please stay behind me too.
後ろにもいてもらって
Can you just sit down and relax like you're bored?
その ままゆっくり退屈割みたいに座ってきてくれる?
Here.
ここに
It's okay to take it slow.
ゆっくりでいいからね
Please get Ash out of here.
アッシュをここから出してもらって
Then, I fell forward.
で、前に倒れて
And I can move like this myself.
で、自分でこうやって動ける
What feels good?
何が気持ちいいんですか?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Just like that.
そのままね
Hold up your hands.
手をね、突っ張って
Hold on.
突っ張って
So, here's a light bean.
で、こっちで軽くビーンに
Move a little further to the right.
もう少し右にグッと
Can it move up and down?
それで上下に動ける?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
cormorant
う
I think Chi-san will appear again.
ち さんまた出そうなんだけど
Where should I put it out?
どこに出したらいいの?